[ GIRL CRYING ]
MAN : Want to see it again , little girl ? It shouldn 't frighten you .
Sorry . Nothing until matinee tomorrow .
[ APPLAUSE ]
MAN : Lady , you mind taking off your hat ? WOMAN : Oh , excuse me .
Attagirl , Janey . Show them how .
[ PEOPLE CLAPPING AND CHEERING ]
All right . Thank you , folks . Thank you .
Thank you very much . Thank you .
One final request , all right ?
[ CROWD YELLING INDISTINCTLY ]
" I 've Written a Letter to Daddy . "
[ PEOPLE CLAPPING ]
All right , all right , all right . Thank you .
" I 've Written a Letter to Daddy . "
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ SINGING ] I 've written a letter to Daddy
His address is heaven above
I 've written , " Dear Daddy , we miss you
And wish you were with us to love "
Instead of a stamp I put kisses
The postman says that 's best to do
I 've written this letter to Daddy
Saying , " I love you "
[ PEOPLE CLAPPING ]
I 've written a letter to Daddy
Saying , " I love you "
[ PEOPLE CLAPPING ]
RAY : Thank you very much .
Well , what do we have here ?
All for you .
Jane , isn 't that a beautiful doll ?
Thank you , young man , that 's gorgeous .
Folks , have you ever seen such a lovely doll ?
All right , children , thank you . Thank you .
Now , folks , please don 't forget there 's a genuine Baby Jane doll
waiting for you out in the foyer . All you have to do is go and collect her .
Remember , you can tell your moms that each and every one
of these genuine , beautiful big dolls is an exact replica
of your own Baby Jane Hudson .
Thank you .
MAN : Baby Jane dolls . Only three and a quarter . There they are .
Very beautiful , natural hair .
[ CHATTERING ]
Baby Jane dolls . Only $ 3.25 .
I won 't ! I don 't wanna go back to that old hotel !
I don 't have to take a nap and you can 't make me !
Don 't act up , sweetheart . You gotta take your nap , you know that .
No , I don 't know , and I 'm not going to !
RAY : Now , Janey , you don 't want all these friends of yours
to think you 're a bad girl , do you ?
I don 't care . I want an ice cream .
- Now , Janey , I told you ... - I want it !
I make the money , so I can have what I want !
Now , Janey , that 's enough .
Leave me alone . I need an ice cream !
WOMAN : If a child of mine ...
Well , if you need an ice cream , I guess you better have some .
I mean , it 's pretty hot and all .
But remember , this is the last time this week .
All right , Daddy . Blanche wants some too .
We gotta have some ice cream for Blanche .
Uh , I ... I don 't want anything .
What do you think you 're trying to do ?
WOMAN 1 : It 's the parents ' fault in cases like this .
WOMAN 2 : I 'm really disappointed .
RAY : Sure is a hot day today .
[ PEOPLE CLAPPING ]
You 're the lucky one , Blanche , really you are .
Someday it 's going to be you getting all the attention .
And when that happens , I ...
I want you to be kinder to Jane and your father than they are to you now .
Do you know what I mean ?
Uh-huh .
I hope you 'll try and remember that .
I won 't forget .
You bet I won 't forget .
WOMAN 1 [ ON SCREEN ] : The agency sent you .
Uh-huh . Think there 's any chance for me ?
WOMAN 1 [ ON SCREEN ] : That depends if Mr. Weber likes you .
WOMAN 2 [ ON SCREEN ] : What type does he like ?
Oh , uh , a lot of personality .
I 'll catch on . Watch me .
Oh , boy , oh , boy , oh , boy .
With my money I should make a picture like that , huh ?
Good morning , Mr. Weber . I 'm Miss Brent .
Oh , yes . Won 't you come a little closer , please ?
She 's got a southern accent like I got a southern accent .
Yeah ?
I know it 's 11 : 00 . I 'll be there when I get there .
Yes , yes , what is it ?
WOMAN [ OVER INTERCOM ] : Mr. Gardner is here to see you .
Gardner ?
I 'll come out .
I 'll be right back , Miss Brent . Help yourself to cigarettes .
- Make yourself at home . - Then the job is mine ?
Need you ask ?
Oh , boy , oh , boy , oh , boy .
Kill it .
What do you think , Ben ?
What 's thinking got to do with it , huh ?
- She stinks , doesn 't she ? - They say the end 's pretty good .
- Maybe we should 've seen it through . - Oh , please .
MAN [ OVER INTERCOM ] : You gonna want that picture again today , Mr. Golden ?
I don 't think anybody 's ever gonna want that picture again .
When the old man hired them Hudson sisters
how come he had to hire the back end of the act too ?
Boy , what a no-talent broad that Baby Jane is .
Why can 't she stay sober ?
Jane 's got her pride . She 's a very sensitive girl .
Your " very sensitive girl " guzzled her way through six cases of Scotch
and slugged two studio cops .
Not to mention one or two other less savory items of publicity
before we got that so-called epic in the can .
Anyway , you don 't have to talk to Jane .
If Blanche would let us out of that clause what says we have to make a picture with Jane
for every picture we make with Blanche
Jane 's contract won 't be any problem .
- See , that 's what we pay lawyers for . - Possibly .
- I can 't see Blanche doing that . - You know , I don 't get it .
Blanche Hudson 's the biggest thing in movies today . She 's got script approval .
She 's got more money than she knows what to do with . Hi .
Hey , she just bought that tremendous place Valentino used to have .
Gonna take her a year to fix it up the way she wants it before they move in .
Well , I guess they can manage to struggle on where they are now .
My point is she ought to have sense enough to know
she can 't make a star out of Baby Jane again .
Blanche doesn 't have any illusions like that .
But she 's a very fine person , Ben .
She 'll never forget those early years
what her sister did for her . She told me that .
Well , I tell you , she 's not doing Baby Jane any favor .
Someday , sooner or later , that girl 's gonna end up in a home .
You 're going to their party at the Grove tonight , aren 't you ?
Did you ever try refusing one of Blanche 's invitations ?
Do me a favor , Marty , will you ? Talk to Blanche .
Try to make her understand , huh ?
- I 'll do my best . - Thanks .
Remind me to send you one of those Baby Jane dolls for Christmas . Ha , ha , ha .
- I 've got mine for this year . - Ha , ha .
I don 't get it , Marty .
What do they make monsters like this for ?
For Blanche Hudson .
That 's our problem .
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
[ BANGING AND CLANGING ]
[ WOMAN SCREAMING ]
[ WOMAN SOBBING ]
[ FOOTSTEPS RECEDING ]
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ON TV ]
MAN [ ON TV ] : You go to bed .
- Hi , Mom . - Oh , hi , dear .
[ LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING ON TV ]
Hello , beautiful . How about a little souvenir ?
- Let go of that , will you ? - Come on , don 't be like that .
Who do you think you 're kidding ?
Thanks .
Isn 't she great ?
Sorry to break in on this fine old Blanche Hudson movie , folks .
But you 'll be glad I did when you see what I have right here
for that favorite pooch of yours .
And Iliad means quality .
So when your dog says " Woof , woof "
feed him Iliad , the classic dog food . - Oh , shut up .
Iliad will bring the sheen ...
My goodness , I remember the first time I saw that picture .
- I thought it was just wonderful . LIZA : When was that ?
Let 's see now . As I recall , your father took me to see it at the old Majestic .
It was before we were married .
Gee , she must be about 150 by now .
As a matter of fact , dear
Blanche Hudson 's just a few years older than I am .
- Really ? - Yes , dear , really .
Well , how come we never see her around ?
We 've been living next door to them for six months now .
And the only one I ever see is that fat sister slouching around .
Don 't they ever have company ? I mean , it must be awful .
You know , Julie says that sister is kind of peculiar .
- Did you ever notice that ? - No , I never have .
Well , that 's what Julie told me .
She said that she was responsible for the accident that crippled her sister Blanche .
Well , that all happened a very long time ago , dear .
Maybe you shouldn 't pay attention to everything Julie tells you .
There 's too many people in this town with nothing to do but talk .
Maybe so , but Julie 's folks have lived here a long time .
I guess she should know .
Turn up the volume , dear . We 're missing the picture .
MAN [ ON TV ] : Will you have champagne ? WOMAN : No . Thanks .
MAN [ ON TV ] : You wanna tell papa your troubles ?
Somebody you love ?
Jack , please try to understand .
I married you because
I was knocked silly and it was a refuge .
I found out tonight that this boy 's in trouble , maybe alone .
It 's blinding me . I can 't think of anything else .
Oh , he should 've held that shot longer .
I told him that when we were rehearsing , also when we shot it .
But he wouldn 't listen .
- How are you ? - Swell .
It 's still a pretty good picture .
And Gemini ...
Ugh .
[ YAWNING ]
[ SOFT MUSIC PLAYS ON TV ]
WOMAN [ ON TV ] : Tommy , you don 't have to say anything .
I 'll just sit here .
JANE : Enjoying yourself ?
Jane , what are you doing ? I was ...
I was watching .
Then you 're an idiot .
I won 't have you speak to me like that .
[ BIRD SQUAWKING ]
Ah , poor thing .
Poor baby .
Quiet down .
[ DOORBELL RINGING ]
Oh . Oh , good morning , Miss Hudson . I hope I 'm not intruding .
I couldn 't resist cutting these for your sister after seeing her show yesterday .
You must be very proud of her new success . On television , I mean .
Yeah .
I can 't tell you how nice it is to be seeing all of her old pictures like this .
I 'll tell her you said so .
You know , my daughter and I would love to meet her one day . Perhaps she could ...
Mrs. Bates , my sister doesn 't ever go out . She 's , um , not fit to receive visitors .
Oh , I am sorry to hear that .
I 'd no idea that ...
Well , um ...
Well , I hope she likes the flowers .
Thanks .
[ BUZZER SOUNDING ]
You miserable ...
[ MOUTHS ] ... bitch .
[ BUZZER CONTINUES SOUNDING ]
Oh , Jane , I 'm sorry . I didn 't mean to ring for my breakfast .
I was just wondering who all those people were at the back door .
Wasn 't anything .
Just that nosy Mrs. Bates going on about your picture last night .
Oh , really ? Did she like it ?
" Oh , really ? Did she like it ? "
She liked it .
I remember when it first came out . It had a tremendous reception .
The critics described it as " brilliant . "
Do you remember what year you made that picture ?
But of course .
You must too . In 1934 , right after I did Moonglow .
I made a picture that year too .
Oh , yes . It was that comedy directed by Lloyd , wasn 't it ?
No , it wasn 't . It was a love story .
The Longest Night .
Marty McDonald said it was the best thing I ever did .
They never even released it in the United States .
Golden was very upset . He told me the company had a bad year and couldn 't ...
No , they had a great year . They didn 't want to show my film .
They were too busy giving a big buildup to that crap you were turning out .
[ BIRD CHIRPING ]
I 'll clean the cage .
[ DOOR CLOSING ]
Oh , that would be Elvira .
Yeah .
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
BLANCHE : Come in , Elvira .
- How are you today ? - Fine .
- Oh , you 've seen Jane . - Uh-huh .
I don 't think she 's feeling very well today .
Did you speak to that Dr. Shelby about Miss Jane like you said ?
No , I haven 't yet . It 's , uh , rather difficult .
I don 't want to upset her again if I can help it .
She 'll be upset anyway , Miss Blanche .
And the longer you leave it , the worse it 's gonna be .
I know .
But I was just hoping it wouldn 't be necessary .
I think she seems much better lately .
It 's none of my business
but she 's been drinking again . You know that ?
No , I hadn 't noticed .
Oh , I don 't think it does her any real harm .
I think I understand her .
Oh , you do , huh ?
Well , then you ought to take a look at this .
- What are these ? - I guess it 's what you 'd call fan mail .
Oh , how kind people are .
You better look at them , then tell me whether or not you 've seen them before .
- Did you read them ? - No .
- But they 've been opened . - That 's right , they all have .
And there 's one in here marked " personal . "
" The other night , my husband and I watched that lovely old movie of yours :
Last Honeymoon . I remember saying to my husband at the time
that seeing you again was just like meeting an old friend . "
Oh , that 's charming . That 's really charming .
The point is you never saw them before , did you ?
No .
I thought not .
I 'm sorry , I thought you ought to know .
But I don 't understand . Where 'd they come from ? Where did you find them ?
In the trash barrel , that 's where .
They 're from that TV station that 's been running your old movies , aren 't they ?
Yes .
- You ... ? You ... ? You mean Jane ? - Who else ?
She must 've thought they were advertisements .
Then why would she open the one marked " personal " ?
And what about this ? You might as well see this too .
Writing those dirty words .
I can 't even remember the last time I saw words like that written down .
But why would she do a thing like this ?
You know what makes her do things like this .
She 's sick , and she 's not getting any better .
In fact , the last month she 's been getting a lot worse .
If you don 't believe me , why are you selling this house and planning to move ?
You said this last month
she 's been a lot worse ? Do you think she knows ?
About selling the house ?
How could she ? You don 't have anything in writing .
We 're sisters , Elvira .
We know each other very well .
I think she 's jealous of those old movies of yours they 're showing on television .
Anyway , in six weeks you 'll hand over the house and then she 'll have to know .
How do I tell her ? How ?
Well , if you 'd just speak to that Dr. Shelby , maybe he could tell her .
No .
No , it ought to be me .
I can 't let a stranger tell her .
But he 's a doctor , Miss Blanche . And she 's a sick woman .
Elvira , you didn 't know her when she was a child .
- When she was young . - I 've seen those pictures she keeps .
Oh , no .
It wasn 't that she was just pretty .
She was different . She was so alive .
I was cleaning the cage .
The bird got out .
But where is it now ?
It flew out the window .
Did you let that bird out on purpose , Miss Jane ?
I just told you , I was cleaning the cage and the bird flew out the window .
I 'm sorry .
She did that on purpose . Believe me , she did it on purpose .
Never mind . Maybe he 'll come back .
Elvira
you won 't change your mind , will you ? About coming to live with me ?
You know I don 't go back on my word , Miss Blanche .
But you 've got to make up your mind about finding somewhere for Miss Jane .
Where they can look after her properly .
I have .
I have made up my mind .
I 'm going to call Dr. Shelby today .
I know , Miss Blanche . I know .
It 's just that I have to be sure I 'm doing the right thing for her .
Hello , is this Johnson 's ?
I want to order some liquor . It 's Jane Hudson .
What do you mean you can 't fill any more orders for me ?
My sister did ?
Well ...
Well , wait a minute . I 'll put her on .
Blanche , would you speak to this man from Johnson 's ?
[ IN BLANCHE 'S VOICE ] Hello .
Who is this , please ?
Oh , yes , Mr. Carson .
Yes , this is Blanche Hudson . What seems to be the trouble ?
I 'm afraid there 's been some misunderstanding .
I certainly didn 't mean to suggest that you shouldn 't fill any orders for her .
After all , we do pay our bills , don 't we ?
Yes , fine .
Would you , please ?
I 'll put her on .
[ IN NORMAL VOICE ] Okay , then ?
Good . Yeah , I 'd like to order
six bottles of Scotch and three bottles of gin .
Yeah , the same brands . And as soon as possible .
I just told Miss Blanche .
I 'm going downtown to see a man about jury duty .
I 'll be back tomorrow .
Hello ?
BLANCHE [ ON PHONE ] : Hello ? Is somebody ... ?
[ JANE PLAYING " I 'VE WRITTEN A LETTER TO DADDY " ON PIANO ]
YOUNG JANE [ SINGING IN JANE 'S MIND ] : I 've written a letter to Daddy
His address is heaven above
I 've written , " Dear Daddy , we miss you
And wish you were with us to love "
Instead of a stamp I put kisses
The postman said ...
[ LAUGHS ]
[ SINGING ] The postman says that 's best to do
I 've written a letter to Daddy
Saying , " I love you "
Now when I 'm very good
And do as I am told
I 'm Mama 's little angel
And Papa says I 'm good as gold
But when I 'm very bad
And answer back and sass
Then I 'm Mama 's little devil
And Papa says I 've got the brass
Now I wish that you would tell me
'Cause I 'm much too young to know
[ SCREAMING ]
[ BUZZER SOUNDING ]
[ SOBBING ]
[ BUZZER CONTINUES SOUNDING ]
All right , Blanche Hudson !
Miss Big , Fat , Movie Star !
Miss Rotten , Stinking Actress !
Press a button , and you think the whole damn world comes running , don 't you ?
" Lunch , Miss Hudson ? "
" Why , certainly , Miss Hudson . "
" I 'm sure we can find something appropriate for you , Miss Hudson ! "
[ PIANO CRASHING ]
Oh , you brought my lunch . A bit early , isn 't it ?
JANE : Then what were you ringing for ?
Oh , I , uh , wanted to tell you something 's wrong with the telephone .
Maybe it 's been left off the hook downstairs .
Is that so ?
Who 'd you wanna call , Blanche ?
Well , actually I ...
I wanted to call Bert Hanley .
JANE : Oh , our business manager .
Yes .
There 's , uh ...
There 's something I 've been meaning to discuss with you .
I ...
Well ?
I 'm afraid I have bad news about money .
You see , the point is
Bert thinks we 'll probably have to sell the house .
Why should we have to sell the house , Blanche ?
Well
that 's what I 'm trying to tell you .
Our , uh , financial position is such that we just , uh ...
- We can 't afford to ... - Got plenty of money invested . I know .
Yes , yes , that 's quite true .
But some of those investments aren 't paying much .
When did our business manager tell you all this ?
Early last week , I think .
He didn 't call here last week . I know that too .
No , we didn 't actually speak on the telephone .
He , um ... He wrote me a letter .
He didn 't write you any letter , either .
- There hasn 't been a letter ... - Yes , there has .
Oh , you 're a liar . You 're just a liar . You always were !
Bert Hanley never wrote you any letter or called you on the phone
telling you to sell the house .
You called him four weeks ago and told him to sell it .
I did nothing of the sort .
Don 't you think I know everything that goes on in this house ?
You 've been spying on me .
Ha ! What do you think ?
You are disgusting .
After all I 've done for you , you spy on me . All I 'm trying to do is help .
Who are you trying to help , Blanche ? !
What are you planning to do with me when you 've sold the house ?
What did you have in mind ? A nice little place where they could look after me ?
Better not tire yourself out using the phone anymore .
If there are any calls , I 'll take them downstairs .
Eat your lunch , it will get cold .
[ DOOR SLAMS ]
Oh !
BLANCHE : Jane , please wait .
Jane . Jane , I want to talk to you .
Please .
Jane , I want to talk to ...
[ PHONE RINGS ]
LIZA : Telephone , Mother .
All right , dear .
BLANCHE : I need your help .
I called this morning and placed an ad .
- Did we give you a reference number ? - Oh , yeah .
Thank you .
All right , there it is .
You want to check the copy ?
[ MUMBLING ]
Yeah , that 's fine .
Did you want this in the personal column or want ads ?
I always think the personal column 's nicer , don 't you ?
Yeah .
Let 's see , that 's an eight-line ad . That will be $ 6.30 .
And , uh , who 's placing this ad ?
- Uh , we have to know . - Why , I am .
Yeah , I know , but who for ?
When you 're placing an ad for someone to do a job for you
we need your name for the record .
Well , my name is Jane Hudson .
Maybe you remember me .
I 'm Baby Jane Hudson .
Oh , uh , sure .
Thank you . This will be in the paper tomorrow .
Who the hell was Baby Jane Hudson ?
[ TYPEWRITER KEYS CLACKING ]
" Please call Dr. Shelby at OL6-1656
and ask him to come here to the house immediately .
Please
under
no
circumstances
let my sister see
the contents
of this note .
Blanche Hudson . "
[ GRUNTING ]
Please .
BATES : Oh , Miss Hudson , how nice to see you .
- I was just going to call on you . JANE : Why ?
BATES : I wanted to ask about the flowers I brought over for your sister .
They don 't last very long this time of year
and I thought perhaps you 'd like some more .
- You could 've saved yourself the trouble . - It is no trouble at all .
I 've just been cutting some , that 's why I came over .
- I always think it 's nice to have flowers ... - Mrs. Bates .
I guess if my sister needed flowers , we could afford to buy them .
Oh , my ...
What 's the matter ? You look like you 've been in a fight .
I 'm not sure that I haven 't been .
That Jane Hudson makes me so mad , I could kill her !
Gee , that 's a good idea .
What will we use ?
Did you have a nice drive ?
- What are you talking about ? - Nothing , dear .
It 's so long since you were out of the house , I thought you 'd gone for a drive .
You know , I was thinking
it 's ever so long since we had a talk .
Uh , you know , a real talk . About the future and everything .
Jane
I didn 't want you to be worried about the house .
Even if I do have to sell it , we 'll still be together .
Blanche , you 're not gonna sell this house .
Daddy bought this house .
And he bought it for me .
You don 't think I remember that , do you ?
You 're wrong , Jane .
You 've just forgotten .
I bought this house for the two of us , when I signed my first contract .
You don 't think I remember anything , do you ?
There are a whole lot of things I remember .
And you never paid for this house .
Baby Jane Hudson made the money that paid for this house , that 's who .
You don 't know what you 're saying .
Blanche
you aren 't ever gonna sell this house .
And you aren 't ever gonna leave it
either .
Jane .
Do you remember when I first came back after the accident ?
You promised you wouldn 't ever talk about that again .
I know I did
but I 'm still in this chair .
After all those years , I 'm still in this chair .
Doesn 't that give you some kind of responsibility ?
Jane , I 'm just trying to explain to you how things really are .
You wouldn 't be able to do these awful things to me if I weren 't in this chair .
But you are , Blanche . You are in that chair !
And tell me , what are these awful things I 'm supposed to be doing to you ?
Well , I ... I ... I meant
you wouldn 't have to work so hard .
And I was thinking maybe ...
Maybe Elvira could come in more often .
Maybe she could even live with us .
We don 't need Elvira .
But
you get so tired , you ...
There 's so much to do , and you 're not well .
Maybe you 're right .
Maybe I should get a checkup or something .
That would be wonderful .
Perhaps we could find a really good doctor .
Yeah , we could get hold of that nice Dr. Shelby , couldn 't we ?
Yeah , let 's see .
What 's his number again ?
" And under no circumstances
tell my sister the contents
of this note . "
It 's not me that needs a doctor , Blanche .
[ PLAYING PIANO ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
Hello , lovey .
Now , don 't stop for me .
- What did the doctor say ? - Oh .
He says it 's no use my trying to go back to work for another six months .
Didn 't he give you anything new to take ?
Oh , he says it 's arthritis .
And the only thing for me to do is not to try and work until it clears up .
Did he suggest what we 're going to use for money in the meantime ?
No , dear . But he 's ever such a nice man .
Now , lovey , never you mind anyway .
You know , we still got a bit of savings .
You 're my little worrier .
Oh , that 's nice . You found something , have you ?
You don 't have to get so excited . You haven 't even seen what it is yet .
No , dear , but it 's a possibility , isn 't it ?
I mean , there aren 't that many jobs that 'd be suitable , I mean
for someone with your qualifications .
What qualifications ?
Uh ... Well , you know , serious music and all that .
[ SLAMS PIANO KEYS ]
Oh , this sounds like just the ticket , doesn 't it ?
- You 're gonna call ? - Call who ?
These people .
- Might as well . - Now ?
Well , it wouldn 't be a lot of bloody use calling next week , would it ?
No , dear .
[ CHUCKLING ]
- Uh , Mom ... - Uh-huh .
- I tell you what .
Why don 't you call for me .
- Tell them you 're my secretary . - All right , dear , I 'll do that .
Now , listen . I won 't let on who I am .
You see , I 'll just tell them I 'm Mr. Flagg 's secretary .
Secretary .
Secretary , huh ?
Well , do you know , I do believe your old mum
would be a jolly good secretary at that .
Don 't you think ?
[ CHUCKLING ]
[ PHONE RINGING ]
Hello ?
Yeah , this is Jane Hudson .
Oh , about the ad .
- Who is this ? - This is Mr. Flagg 's secretary .
Oh , his secretary .
Yes . Mr. Flagg is very interested
and he 'd like to know if he could have an appointment .
I think you 'll find he 's very well-qualified .
Sure , I 'd be glad to give Mr. Flagg an appointment .
Well , now , let me see , um ...
How about 4 this afternoon ?
[ WHISPERING ] Four this afternoon ?
[ IN NORMAL VOICE ] I think that would be fine .
Well , I 'll be expecting him then .
Thanks .
It 's all fixed , lovey .
Your old mum has managed everything
hasn 't she ?
[ BUZZER SOUNDING ]
Oh , shut up !
Stop it !
- What do you want this time ? - Who was on the telephone ?
None of your business . What were you ringing for ?
- I 'm hungry , Jane . - Of course you 're hungry .
You didn 't eat your dinner , that 's why you 're hungry .
But you forgot my breakfast .
I didn 't forget your breakfast .
I didn 't bring you breakfast
because you didn 't eat your din-din .
Ha !
You know , we 're right back where we started .
When I was on the stage , you depended on me for everything .
Even the food you ate came from me .
Now you have to depend on me for your food again .
So we 're right back where we started .
Why are you doing this to me ?
Why ?
Doing what ?
Making me afraid to eat , trying to make me starve myself .
Don 't be silly .
If you starve , you die .
I don 't know what you 're talking about . You really must be sick .
Jane .
Did you ever stop to think that
if anything happened to me , I mean , anything bad
there wouldn 't be any money for you ?
I wouldn 't be here to sign the checks .
You wouldn 't even have pocket money .
Did you ever think of that ?
Yeah , I 've thought about that .
Why didn 't you eat your dinner ?
Because I 'm afraid . You made me afraid .
Ha !
I thought you were supposed to be the big girl in this family .
Nothing wrong with it .
You 're just a neurotic , Blanche .
You know what ? You 're just a neurotic .
- Good morning , Elvira . - Good morning .
- Please , Jane , I 'm so hungry . - I have to go now .
But just a little , please .
No . You didn 't eat your din-din , so you 'll have to wait till lunchtime .
Oh , Jane , please , don 't do this to me .
Jane ! Jane , please !
JANE : Good morning , Elvira . - Good morning , Miss Jane .
I wanna talk to you .
- I want to apologize . - Apologize ?
Yeah , I wasn 't feeling so well yesterday , so I was unkind to you .
I want to make it up .
I got up this morning and fixed the house .
So you can have the whole day off .
Here 's your $ 15 .
Thanks , but does Miss ... ?
What I mean is , does Miss Blanche know about my taking the day off ?
Oh , sure , she knows .
All right , if you say so .
- See you next Tuesday then . - Yeah .
- Have a good time . - Bye .
Bye .
[ CLATTERING ]
Who was that at the door earlier ?
Elvira .
Where is she now ? In the kitchen ?
No . I gave her the day off .
She has a pretty hard time , considering .
I told her to come back next week .
Oh , Blanche .
You know we got rats in the cellar ?
No ...
Oh !
[ LAUGHING ]
[ MOANING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ BLANCHE SOBBING AND JANE LAUGHING ]
[ DOORBELL RINGING ]
Good afternoon .
- Mr. Flagg ? - Yes , I 'm Edwin Flagg .
I have an appointment with a Miss Hudson for 4 : 00 .
I 'm Jane Hudson .
My , you 're right on time , aren 't you ?
Yes . Yes , I believe I am .
Come in .
We can talk here in the living room .
Oh .
I say , what a perfectly charming room .
- So you 're Edwin Flagg ? - Yes , that 's right .
I 'll bring in some tea . You like tea ?
Oh , yes . I 'm quite fond of tea .
You must 've guessed that I 'm English .
Oh , really ? How nice for you .
Mis ... !
EDWIN : Oh , here , let me help you .
That 's a terribly big burden for such a little girl .
JANE : Thank you . You 're very kind .
It 's so hot today . Did you drive here in your car ?
EDWIN : Well , actually , I took a cab .
It 's a bit of a nuisance , but I had to put my car in for servicing .
- Cream or lemon ? - Cream .
Sugar ?
My , it looks good .
I always think it 's nice to break bread with strangers , don 't you ?
Oh , yes . Yes , indeed .
I don 't think you actually mentioned the exact nature of ...
I 've been retired for some time , taking care of someone who 's sick .
Now you 're free to return to your profession ?
- Yes . - And what exactly ?
I mean , I take it you 're a soloist . Some instrument ?
I wonder if you can guess who I am .
Can you give me a hint ?
Well , it 's not really fair to make you guess . I 'm ...
I 'm Baby Jane Hudson .
Oh !
Do you mean you 're really the Baby Jane Hudson ?
Yes , I am .
And I 'm going to revive my act exactly as I used to do it .
The arrangements will have to be brought up-to-date .
Music changes so much , doesn 't it ?
And they 're desperate for new acts : Television , Las Vegas , and all the clubs .
Well , there are a lot of people who remember me , lots of them .
I don 't see how you could fail .
Oh .
You know , I had a kind of a feeling
the minute I opened that door and saw you .
I just knew we were going to be friends .
- I 've been thinking about costumes . - Costumes ?
I took some of my old ones down to be copied .
- Do you think that 's a good idea ? - Of course .
Of course , I don 't quite remember ...
How silly of me , Edwin . How could you ?
But I do want your opinion . I really do . All my scrapbooks and stuff
are in the rehearsal room . You can look at them and tell me what you think .
- You 'd like to see them , wouldn 't you ? - Well , of course .
Oh , I wish Daddy could be here right now .
" You can never lose your talent , " he used to tell me .
" You can lose everything else but you can 't lose your talent . "
Come on .
I think you 'll find these clippings very interesting .
Daddy saved them for me from the very first .
He used to put them in special books .
I always liked that picture . It 's so ...
It 's so sad .
[ BUZZER SOUNDING ]
- Will you excuse me ? - Certainly .
You always spoil everything , don 't you ?
BLANCHE : No . I just wanted to know ... - Who is down there ? I 'll tell you .
I got a friend down there . Someone who 's come to see me .
He doesn 't even know you exist . You don 't like that , do you ?
You 're wrong . I 've always wanted you to have friends .
- That 's what I always wanted . - How come I never had any ?
Well , maybe you weren 't ...
I mean , maybe you were just too independent .
No , that 's not why . You always stopped me from having friends , that 's why .
Not anymore , Jane . Not anymore .
I 'm pleased that you have a friend . That 's what you need .
- Oh , sure . - I was just hoping maybe
I could meet him and we could have a nice talk , just the three of us .
You 'd like that , wouldn 't you ? You could tell him a whole lot of lies about me .
Scare him off
or maybe have him for yourself .
[ EDWIN PLAYING " I 'VE WRITTEN A LETTER TO DADDY " ]
[ SINGING ] I 've written a letter to Daddy
His address is heaven above
That 's wonderful .
[ PIANO PLAYING ]
[ SINGING ] I 've written a letter to Daddy
His address is heaven above
I 've written , " Dear Daddy , we miss you
And wish you were with us to love "
Instead of a stamp I put kisses
The postman says that 's best to do
I 've written a letter to Daddy
Saying , " I love you "
Saying
" I love you "
Edwin , you certainly can play , can 't you ?
- And you certainly can sing . - Oh , thank you .
I can see you 've done this kind of work before .
No , not really . Actually , I 've spent most of my time on serious music .
Composing and that sort of thing .
This will be your first contact with show business ?
Not exactly .
You see , my father was quite well-known as an actor .
In the movies ? Maybe I worked with him .
I shouldn 't think so .
He 's been dead quite a long time now .
I lost my daddy when I was quite young too .
Of course , he was more in the classical tradition as an actor .
Shakespeare and that sort of thing .
People used to say Daddy could 've been a star in his own right .
- He was a musician too . - Oh ? What instrument ?
Piano and banjo .
Oh .
That 's very interesting . The banjo 's a very native American instrument .
Of course , my father was British
but he never really got a chance out here in Hollywood .
That 's too bad .
It 's funny , really .
Because actually he came from a rather distinguished family , socially
yet nearly all the parts he had were playing menials , butlers and such .
- Oh , really ? - Yes .
I don 't think my mother ever really appreciated
what he was trying to do .
Oh , I know what you mean .
It 's very hard for an artist when people don 't understand .
- I remember when ... - I try to explain to her
that if you 're going to produce anything decent
in the way of serious music
you must have the right atmosphere .
But of course , Dehlia can 't understand that .
Dehlia ? Who 's Dehlia ?
You might not think it to look at her , but she 's my mother .
Oh . For a minute , I thought you had
a wife or a lady friend tucked away somewhere .
Oh , no . No .
Oh , no , there 's nothing like that .
How much were you actually thinking of paying ?
Paying ?
Well , what do you think ?
How about $ 100 ?
A week , of course .
Well , I ...
- I think that would be fair . - Then that 's settled .
I don 't like talking about money , do you ?
No . It 's not that important , is it ? Not like relationships between people .
The thing is , if I 'm going to move out and give up my pupils
I 'll have to know for sure .
When are you thinking of starting ?
Just when could you let me have some money ?
Well , I 've got some family matters to take care of .
That should take about a week or so .
Well , then I don 't see why we couldn 't start rehearsing right away .
EDWIN : Mm-hm .
Tell you what , Edwin
I 'll pay you first thing Wednesday , a month in advance .
It 's done . Ha-ha-ha .
How about going to dinner somewhere ? Somewhere nice ?
- That sounds fine . - I 'll tell you what .
Why don 't you come with me now . I 've got to pick up my costumes .
- We could go on to dinner from there . - Oh ...
I promised my ... Dehlia I 'd be home for supper .
Oh . Well , I 'll drive you home then .
I 'm so excited .
You know , I know everything is going to go just marvelously for both of us .
I have to go up and change . I won 't be a minute .
[ JANE GIGGLES ]
[ CAR STARTS ]
EDWIN : This is really a rather charming neighborhood .
JANE : Yes , I 've always found it very pleasant .
I just can 't wait to get started on rehearsals .
We 're gonna be a great team , the two of us .
EDWIN : Oh , I 'm sure we are .
I 'll see you Wednesday .
- Bye . - Bye .
[ GRUNTING ]
[ PANTING ]
[ MOANS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
This is Blanche . Blanche Hudson .
I need your help . Is the doctor there ? I must talk to him .
Well , he 's with a patient right now .
But I have to talk to him . I 've got to .
Hold on , please . I 'll see if I can interrupt him .
- Dr. Shelby ? - Yes , Blanche .
Miss Hill tells me you 're a little upset . What 's the trouble ?
BLANCHE : You must come . I need you here .
No . It 's about my sister .
I need your help . I need you here .
Here at the house .
No . No , it 's nothing like that .
It 's the way she 's behaving .
You 've got to come over right away . Please , before she comes back .
I don 't quite understand .
Is this an emotional disturbance you 're talking about ?
Yes , she 's emotionally disturbed .
She 's unbalanced .
I don 't know , doctor . I mean ...
- Are you trying to tell me she 's violent ? - Yes . Yes , she is .
I 'm ...
I 'm not sure .
I ...
[ STAMMERING ]
Very well . We aren 't getting anywhere like this .
I 'll come over right away .
That ... That ... That was ...
I know who it was .
No , Jane , it really was .
And I know what you 're trying to do .
I 'm not trying to do anything . Honestly , Jane .
BLANCHE : Aah !
[ BLANCHE GRUNTS ]
JANE : You ...
[ GASPS ]
[ IN BLANCHE 'S VOICE ] This is Blanche Hudson again .
Could I speak to the doctor ?
Yes , certainly . Hold on , please . I 'll try and catch him . Doctor Shelby .
- Hello , Blanche . I 'm on my way now . - Oh , I 'm so glad I caught you in time .
Dr. Shelby , we 're not going to need you after all .
I know , but Jane has gone to another doctor .
- Another doctor ? - Yes . Another doctor .
Well , if she 's chosen to go to someone else ...
[ JANE LAUGHS ]
JANE : After all , we really can 't interfere , can we
if Jane 's chosen to go to another doctor ?
I 'm very sorry .
[ IN NORMAL VOICE ] Goodbye , doctor .
I thought I told you not to come back till next week .
I know , but I had a free day
so I thought I 'd come by and see if anything needed doing .
There isn 't anything , so you could 've saved yourself the trouble .
I was gonna write you a note , but now I may as well tell you .
We 're not going to be needing you anymore .
But I don 't understand .
We 're closing up the house . Blanche wants a place at the beach .
The doctor thinks that 's best for her , so that 's what we 're gonna do .
Don 't worry , you 'll be paid for today . I 'll send you a check .
I 'm not worried about any pay . I 'd just like to see Miss Blanche before I go .
Well , you can 't . She 's asleep .
That 's all right . I don 't mind waiting .
Well , I do . I 've gotta leave , so just give me the keys to the house .
I 'm sorry , I don 't have the keys . I must 've left them at home .
Anyway , go . You 're fired .
[ HONKING HORN ]
ELVIRA : Miss Blanche ?
Miss Blanche ?
Miss Blanche , are you awake ?
Miss Blanche !
Are you all right in there ?
Wait , now , and I 'll go find a key .
Thank you .
WOMAN : Good morning , Miss Hudson . - Good morning .
How 's Miss Blanche these days ?
She 's just fine .
Your deposit slip ?
Um , well , Blanche wanted me to get it all in cash this time .
- I guess she has some special reason . - Yes , but doesn 't she normally ... ?
I mean , if she isn 't going to deposit her monthly check
she usually gives us a call and tells us what she wants us to do .
- Didn 't she call ? - I don 't think so .
Oh , I guess she must still be asleep . She gave me that check last night .
I see . Just a moment , please .
I guess it will be all right , Miss Hudson .
- Fifties and 20s all right ? - Yes , please .
- There you are . - Thank you .
Bye , now .
Miss Blanche , I 'll tell you right now , if that sister of yours
has gone and given you sleeping tablets to keep you quiet
while she 's out doing I don 't know what
I 'm sure as hell gonna call the police on her .
It 's all right , Miss Blanche .
BATES : Oh , Miss Hudson !
I 'm glad I caught you .
I hope you don 't mind . There 's something I 've been meaning to ask you .
- What ? - Well , I 'm kind of short of help
around the house .
I was wondering if you 'd mind your cleaning lady giving me a couple of days .
As far as I 'm concerned , you can have her as often as you want .
My sister and I are moving , so we won 't want her anymore .
But you 'll have to call her because she isn 't here . I 've already sent her home .
But I just saw her .
Yes , but I sent her home .
No , but that 's impossible .
I saw her go in the house a few minutes ago .
- In the house ? - Yes .
So you finally decided to come back , huh ?
What are you doing here ?
- I told you you 're fired . - Never mind all that .
I want to know what 's going on around here .
- But you said you didn 't have your key . - It just so happens that I did .
So now you can tell me what you mean by locking Miss Blanche in her room .
This isn 't her house . This is mine and I can do what I like .
It doesn 't make a bit of difference whose it is . Act like a grown woman .
Suppose there was a fire and she was locked in her room ?
Well , there wasn 't .
You open that door and stop all this nonsense !
- No . - Then give me the key .
No .
She 's asleep . I gave her a pill .
You did , huh ?
Then you better give me that key and be quick about it .
I won 't and you can 't make me . I 'm not afraid of you .
All right , Miss Hudson . I 'm not going to fool with you .
If you won 't give me that key , I 'll go right down and call the police .
You 'll be sorry .
Give me that key .
- I didn 't mean her any harm . - You better not have done her any harm .
My God , Miss Blanche .
What has she done to you ?
[ MOANING ]
ELVIRA : I 'll get it off in a minute .
Don 't worry , Miss Blanche . I 'll get you down from here .
I know , Miss Blanche . I know .
You just rest easy .
Going out , are you , dear ?
- You know I am . - Having dinner with her ?
EDWIN : Uh-huh .
DEHLIA : I 'm forgotten .
Now , you won 't be back too late , will you , lovey , huh ?
[ EDWIN WHISTLING ]
Who knows ?
You could 've been better than all of them .
But they didn 't want that .
They just didn 't love you enough .
You know that ? They just didn 't love you enough .
[ DOORBELL RINGING ]
Edwin ?
Miss Hudson ?
I 'm sorry , Edwin .
I can 't let you in .
Not now .
Oh , to hell with it !
I can 't let you in .
Not now .
[ GROANING ]
What am I going to do ?
[ SOBBING ]
What ... ? What am I going to do ?
I don 't know .
Oh , Miss Hudson , I thought ...
I didn 't know there was anyone in here .
I just came home and I saw a light
and I thought perhaps you 'd left the lights of your car on .
- I 've had that happen to me . - That 's all right , Mrs. Bates .
I had that happen to me once . It 's no joke .
Wake up in the morning and find you 've got a dead battery .
No joke .
Well , uh , as long as everything 's all right , I guess I 'll just say good night .
Good night .
[ RINGING ]
EDWIN : That doesn 't prove anything .
Now what do you think you 'll do ?
I 'll manage , lovey .
- I suppose you think I 'm making this up . - I wouldn 't know .
Hazel should know , shouldn 't she ?
She worked in the same studio when it all happened .
Just after one of those studio parties
and right in front of her own house .
Jane Hudson drove a car straight at her own sister and crippled her for life .
- Come on , you mean she tried to kill her ? - Yes , she did .
She tried to murder her own sister .
- How is it they didn 't arrest her then ? - They would 've
but the studio had it all hushed up on account of Blanche Hudson 's career .
- That sounds very likely . - Yes , doesn 't it ?
The fine woman you 've chosen to run around with turns out to be broke
and a murderer as well .
- I see ! - Well , it 's true !
All right then , I 'll ask her about it when I see her again .
You wouldn 't see a woman like that again .
Why not ? You just told me she 's got a rich sister .
You haven 't heard the worst of it yet .
- You mean there 's more ? - Yes , there is .
After she 'd run down her own sister , your precious Jane Hudson
ran off and left her there to die , like some poor animal .
She ran off and disappeared for three whole days .
What happened then ? Don 't tell me they couldn 't find her .
They found her , all right .
They found her , all right . They found her in some hotel room
with a man that she 'd never even seen before .
Well , why should that upset you ?
Isn 't that how I was conceived ?
Oh .
[ PHONE RINGING ]
Hello .
Yes , this is Miss Hudson .
She left .
About a week ago .
Uh-huh .
We have a report here filed by her cousin , listing her as a missing person .
Did she tell you what her plans were , anything like that ?
No , I don 't know a thing .
We have other addresses to check . Maybe we 'll come up with something .
Otherwise we 'll probably be getting in touch with you again .
Meanwhile , if you do hear from her , we 'd appreciate you letting us know .
Good night .
Blanche !
The police are looking for Elvira .
It wasn 't my fault . She wouldn 't go away .
You heard her , she wouldn 't leave me alone .
I don 't know what to do , Blanche . What am I going to do ?
What am I going to do ?
If they find her , we 'll have to run away .
That 's what we 'll do . We 'll just go away .
But then I wouldn 't see Edwin anymore .
He wouldn 't like what I did .
It wasn 't my fault , but he wouldn 't like what I did .
I don 't care . We 'll go to the beach .
We 'll go and live at the seashore all the time , like we used to
when I was little and Daddy was there .
And then ... And maybe we 'll have friends .
People would come and see us . Oh , I 'd like that .
Blanche .
Blanche , listen to me .
You know I always wanted everything to be nice , don 't you ?
I don 't see how Elvira could make me do a thing like that .
I just don 't understand .
It was like that time in the hotel room
when they came and told me that you were hurt and that I 'd done it .
And there was a big man there , a policeman
and he hit me and he slapped me
and I tried to tell him that I couldn 't do a thing like that .
Not to my own sister .
Jane ...
JANE : He said I was a liar .
The accident , it ...
No , it wasn 't an accident .
- I did it . You told me so yourself . - But I ...
I , um ... I must tell you .
I don 't want to talk about it !
Every time I think about something nice , you remind me of the bad things .
I only want to talk about the nice things .
Remember when Daddy and I used to rehearse at the beach ?
I 'd be dancing on the sand
and all the people would come and watch .
All crowd around to see Baby Jane Hudson .
[ DOORBELL RINGING ]
What will I do ?
BLANCHE : Let them in . - Oh , but what if ... ?
It may be Edwin .
Of course .
It 's Edwin .
Edwin !
You want to make him tell on me .
- No . No , Jane . No , Jane . No , Jane . - Yes . Yes .
No , Jane . Please .
There .
Edwin !
Wait for me .
OFFICER : Miss Jane Hudson ?
- Yes ? - I 'm sorry , Miss Hudson
but we just picked up this young man in front of your house .
Says he 's on his way in to see you .
Is that right ?
- I don 't understand . EDWIN : They 're trying to say I 'm drunk .
We 'll just say that you 're a little happy , okay ?
Who 's happy ?
I 'm not happy .
EDWIN : So now you know . - That 's right . So now we know .
Sorry to have bothered you , Miss Hudson . Good night .
Good night .
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
I have the money . Really , I have . But don 't be mean to me .
- You promised me . - I know I did and I have the money .
Look , let 's go in the kitchen , and have a drink together .
It 's nice there . And then we can be friends again .
- And everything . - And everything .
- I 've got something else for you . - What ?
It 's a surprise . Would you like to have a ?
You 're gonna like your present .
You 're really gonna like it .
Drink your drink , Edwin .
I 'll go get it for you .
This is my very own .
It 's a genuine Baby Jane doll .
I used to give them to all my really good friends
the people that I worked with .
- They made them for me . - Marvelous .
- Specially . - Very lifelike .
Now , Jane , you talk to nice Mr. Flagg
and nice Mr. Flagg will have his money in a minute .
Oh , you 're not comfy like that , are you ?
Let 's go bye-bye .
Whoo !
Here comes the Super Chief !
[ EDWIN LAUGHING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Edwin ! Edwin ! Stop it !
[ THUMPING AND CLATTERING ]
What was that ?
Nothing . It 's nothing . I didn 't do anything .
Edwin . Edwin . Edwin , please .
She 'll take you away from me .
BLANCHE : Please , help me .
Please .
Help me .
She 's dying .
For God 's sake .
- Edwin ... ! - Get away from me ! Get away from me !
Edwin , I 've got your money .
Edwin , you forgot your money !
[ FOOTSTEPS RECEDING ]
He hates me .
Hey , stop .
He 's going to tell .
Eddie 's going to tell !
Blanche .
You 've got to help me .
We 've got to leave .
Please .
Please , Blanche .
Help me .
Please .
[ GRUNTING ]
Please help me . You 've got to .
You got to .
I like this place .
We can just sit here for a while .
And pretty soon the sun will come up and it will be nice .
You should look at the sea .
It has all lights on it .
You used to like that .
[ PEOPLE LAUGHING AND CHATTERING ]
[ UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO ]
MAN [ ON RADIO ] : We interrupt this program
to bring you a special news bulletin .
At 11 : 25 this morning , local law enforcement agencies
had assigned special details to the kidnap-slaying mystery
that surrounds the Hudson sisters .
It 's believed Blanche Hudson , film great of the early ' 30s ...
- Ernie . Get a load of this . ... was abducted by her sister
Baby Jane Hudson , from the family home on McCadden in Hollywood
sometime between the hours of 10 p.m. And 10 : 30 p.m. Last evening .
With the exception of one witness
who reportedly saw the Hudson car , a 1940 or 1941 black convertible
heading west on Wilshire and Santa Monica
no report has been received to date concerning the missing sisters .
The following is a police ...
- So you found that colored woman . - Yeah , they found her , all right .
Sure is a rotten way to get your picture in the paper .
You reckon you 'll ever find that Baby Jane
or whatever her name is ? - Sure , we 'll find her .
But I guess maybe it 'll be too late .
- Well , thanks for the empties . - Thanks .
Oh , officer , there 's a car down there parked right out in the road .
I almost got stuck in the sand when I tried to get around it .
MAN 1 : You mean that old Lincoln convertible ?
MAN 2 : That 's right .
MAN 1 : Yeah , that was parked there when we opened up this morning .
MAN 2 : The keys are there , but I didn 't want to move it . I thought maybe ...
What do you figure ?
Cops . How do you figure cops ?
This is it .
You must be hot .
Jane .
Help me .
I 'm afraid .
Find someone .
- A doctor . - I can 't .
If I die
you 'll be alone .
But they 'd be mean to me like they were before .
They 'll be kind .
I don 't want to hear .
Jane , I 'm ...
I 'm dying .
There 's no time .
You must listen .
I made you waste your whole life
thinking you 'd crippled me .
Please stop .
You didn 't do it , Jane .
I did it myself .
Don 't you understand ?
I crippled myself .
You weren 't driving that night .
You weren 't driving .
You were too drunk . I wouldn 't let you drive .
I made you go open the gates .
I watched you get out of the car .
You 'd been so cruel to me at the party .
Imitating me .
Making people laugh at me .
I watched you get out of the car .
I wanted to run you down .
Crush you .
But you saw the car coming .
I hit the gates .
I snapped my spine .
Then you mean
all this time we could 've been friends ?
You were frightened and ran away .
I managed to crawl out of the car , up to the gates .
When they found me
they assumed it was your fault .
You were so drunk and confused . You didn 't know any better .
You weren 't ugly then .
I made you that way .
I even did that .
There 's a place up there that sells things .
You like ice cream ?
I 'll get you some .
Thank you .
- Yeah . - Do you have ice cream ?
Yes , what flavor ?
Well ...
Vanilla , coffee , strawberry , lemon ...
Strawberry . Strawberry , please . Two big strawberries , please .
- It 's gonna be 40 cents . - Thanks .
Right . You better send some more help .
Miss Hudson . Miss Hudson !
We 've been looking all over for you , Miss Hudson .
I 'm sorry , but we must find your sister .
- Is she here on the beach with you ? - Yes , she is .
- I 'll take these for you . - Oh , no , they 're mine .
They 're for my sister Blanche .
She 's going to be a movie star , did you know that ?
That 's right , miss .
We want to find your sister because I think maybe she needs help .
I think maybe she 's in trouble .
Won 't you show us where she is , please ?
Won 't you take us to her ? Please , Miss Hudson .
WOMAN 1 : She must be some kind of nut ...
MAN : Hey , lady , where you taking those cones ?
WOMAN 2 : Boy , she 's a little nutty .
[ PEOPLE CHATTERING ]
WOMAN 3 : Look at her now .
[ English - US - SDH ]